

stefano.dallona@gmail.com



33082, Azzano Decimo - Italy

## **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Science
University of Trento
Computer Science
107/110 Awarded at IS2\_2023
Trento, Italy | November 2023

Master of Science University of Padua Geological And Earth Sciences 110/100 with honours Padua, Italy | December 1999

### **CERTIFICATIONS**

Certified Scrum Master Scrum Alliance Porcia, Italy | April 2018

Computer Networks Specialist ASSISTAL Padua, Italy | December 2000

### **LANGUAGES**

**English** 

Proficiency (C2)

# STEFANO DALLONA

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Passionate DevOps Engineering with 5-years' experience in the role and a solid development background gained over 15 years spent in application design and development. Expert in problem solving and agile methodologies. Familiar with working in big companies, in cross-cultural, global teams.

### SKILLS

- Infrastructure Automation
- Continuous Integration / Continuous Deployment
- Agile Methodologies
- Containerization Technologies
- Testing and Debugging
- Monitoring and Logging

- Microservices Architecture
- Web-Based Software Engineering
- Full-Stack Development
- Scripting Languages: Groovy, Python
- Programming Languages: JavaScript, Java, Python, Scala
- Frameworks: React, JSF, JSP, Spring, Spring Boot, Flask, D3.js

#### **WORK HISTORY**

Electrolux - Senior DevOps Engineer, Pordenone

October 2019 - Current

Managed the company global DevOps infrastructure based on Atlassian suite. Administered the company Application Monitoring solution (APM) based on Dynatrace One Agent SaaS.

Developed CI/CD pipelines to automate web applications build and deploy.

**Electrolux - Java Software Engineer**, Pordenone

January 2014 - September 2019

Designed and developed Web applications based on Domain Driven Design paradigm and Microservices Architecture.

Acquired deep knowledge of manufacturing processes, especially in the field of Production Planning, Procurement, Material Requirements Planning and Incoming Flows Management.

Electrolux - Java Software Developer, Pordenone

April 2007 - December 2013

Contributed to the development of several modules of the proprietary Java-based ERP, used by the company's factories to support the manufacturing processes.